<odoo>
    <data noupdate="0">

        <!--Request For Re-registration-->
        <record id="email_template_re_registration_request" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Re-Registration Request - Send by Email</field>
            <field name="subject">Request for Re-Registration</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="model_re_reg_waiting_responce_parents"/>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
            <field name="body_html"><![CDATA[
                <div style="font-family: 'Lucica Grande', Ubuntu, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; color: rgb(34, 34, 34); background-color: #FFF; ">
                    <p>Dear ${object.name.name},</p>
                    <p>Thank you for entrusting your child to our school. As we go forward, we request you to kindly
                     complete the re-registration process to ensure a place for your child(ren) in the next academic year.</p>
                    <p>To secure a place in the next academic year, you would have to pay an amount of AED 1000.
                     This deposit is <b>non-refundable</b> should a student not take up the
                     confirmed place in, April, but is fully adjustable against the first term fees. The deposit may be
                     paid online using our online Payment gateway (Online transaction charges may apply), in person at
                     the school fee counter or via bank transfer.</p>
                     <p>Kindly complete this process before the close of the academic year ( the exact date has been
                     appended at the end of the email) so as to help us enlist your child in the next academic year.
                     The school will be unable to confirm a seat, if the re-registration process is not completed for
                     any reasons.</p>
                    <p>Our school teams are happy to help if you need any further details regarding re-registration or
                     have queries regarding the process. Please contact our Registration Team or Accounts Department at
                     the address given below.</p>
                    
                </div>
            ]]></field>
        </record>

                     <!--Resend Request For Re-registration for PARENT-->
        <record id="email_template_resend_re_registration_request_parent" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Resend Re-Registration Request for parent- Send by Email</field>
            <field name="subject">Resend Request for Re-Registration</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="model_re_reg_waiting_responce_parents"/>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
            <field name="body_html"><![CDATA[
                <div style="font-family: 'Lucica Grande', Ubuntu, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; color: rgb(34, 34, 34); background-color: #FFF; ">

                    <p>Dear ${object.name.name},</p>
                    <p>Greetings!!</p>
                    <p>This is a kind reminder for re-registration of your child(ren) for the next academic year
                    ${object.request_batch_id.name}.</p>
                    <p>As informed earlier it is imperative for the child to be re-registered so as to confirm a place
                    for him/her in the next academic year. You are requested to refer to the link appended to the end of
                     this email and fill in the re-registration form for your ward(s).</p>
                   <p>To secure a place in the next academic year, you would have to pay an amount of AED 1000.
                    This deposit is non-refundable should a student not take up the confirmed place in April,
                    but is fully adjustable against the first term fees. The deposit may be paid online with a credit card,
                     in person at the school fee counter or via bank transfer.</p>
                    <p>Thank you for entrusting your child to our school.</p>
                    <p>If you require any further details regarding re-registration or have questions regarding the process,
                    please contact our Registration Team or Accounts Department at the address given below.</p>
                    <p>We once again appreciate your support to us and look forward for a long and trusted connection ahead.</p>
                  
                </div>
            ]]></field>
        </record>

                 <!--Resend Request For Re-registration for STUDENT-->
        <record id="email_template_resend_re_registration_request_student" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Resend Re-Registration Request for student- Send by Email</field>
            <field name="subject">Resend Request for Re-Registration</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="model_re_reg_waiting_responce_student"/>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
            <field name="body_html"><![CDATA[
                <div style="font-family: 'Lucica Grande', Ubuntu, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; color: rgb(34, 34, 34); background-color: #FFF; ">

                    <p>Dear ${object.name.parents1_id.name},</p>
                    <p>Greetings!!</p>
                    <p>This is a kind reminder for re-registration of your child(ren) for the next academic year
                    ${object.next_year_batch_id.name}.</p>
                    <p>As informed earlier it is imperative for the child to be re-registered so as to confirm a place
                    for him/her in the next academic year. You are requested to refer to the link appended to the end of
                     this email and fill in the re-registration form for your ward(s).</p>
                   <p>To secure a place in the next academic year, you would have to pay an amount of AED 1000.
                    This deposit is non-refundable should a student not take up the confirmed place in April,
                    but is fully adjustable against the first term fees. The deposit may be paid online with a credit card,
                     in person at the school fee counter or via bank transfer.</p>
                    <p>Thank you for entrusting your child to our school.</p>
                    <p>If you require any further details regarding re-registration or have questions regarding the process,
                    please contact our Registration Team or Accounts Department at the address given below.</p>
                    <p>We once again appreciate your support to us and look forward for a long and trusted connection ahead.</p>
                   
                </div>
            ]]></field>
        </record>

                <!--Re-registration Confirmation-->
        <record id="email_template_re_registration_confirmation" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Re-Registration Confirmation - Send by Email</field>
            <field name="subject">Re-registration Confirmation for your ward(s)</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="model_re_reg_waiting_responce_parents"/>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
            <field name="body_html"><![CDATA[
                <div style="font-family: 'Lucica Grande', Ubuntu, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; color: rgb(34, 34, 34); background-color: #FFF; ">
                    <p>Dear ${object.name.name},</p>
                    <p></p>
                    <p>We have received your inputs regarding the re-registration of your ward(s) and the
                    re-registration status and fee details are in the table appended below in the email.</p>
                    <p>If you have answered with a YES to any of the fields in the summary provided in the appended
                    table, you are requested to pay the applicable re-registration fees towards confirmation of the
                    re-registration process for your child. All advance payments made shall be adjusted to the
                    re-registration fee. Online payment transaction charges may apply and the amount mentioned in
                    the online fee payment link may vary accordingly.</p>
                    <p>If you have a NO in the confirmation column, we assume your ward(s) shall not be continuing
                    with us in the next academic year.</p>
                   
                    <p>All fee payments can be paid:</p>
                    <p>1. By cash at the fee counter in school</p>
                    <p>2. By bank transfer</p>
                    <p>3. By Cheque, deposited at the fee counter in school.</p>
                    <p>4. By using the following link to pay online using our online payment gateway-PayFort<p>
                    <p>The amount paid towards re-registration is collected as advance and will be adjusted in next
                    year's academic fee.</p>
                    <p>Thank you for your prompt response and confirmation.</p>
                    <p>We wish your child(ren) better prospects in the next grade.</p>
                    
                </div>
            ]]></field>
        </record>

        <!--Receipt-->
        <record id="email_template_re_registration_fee_receipt_paid" model="mail.template">
            <field name="name">Re-Registration fee receipt - Send by Email</field>
            <field name="subject">Re-Registration Fee Receipt</field>
            <field name="model_id" ref="account.model_account_payment"/>
            <field name="auto_delete" eval="True"/>
            <field name="report_template" ref="edsys_edu_fee.action_student_payment_receipt"/>
            <field name="report_name">Re_reg_fee_receipt</field>
            <field name="body_html"><![CDATA[
            <div style="font-family: 'Lucica Grande', Ubuntu, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif; font-size: 12px; color: rgb(34, 34, 34); background-color: #FFF; ">

                <p>Dear ${object.partner_id.parents1_id.name},</p>
                <p></p>
                <p>Thank you for completing the re-registration process by paying the re-registration advance and
                 confirming a place for your child(ren) in the next academic year. Please find the receipt for the
                 payment made, appended below in this email.</p>
                <p>The amount paid towards re-registration is collected as advance and will be adjusted in next year
                 academic fee.</p>
                <p>Thank you for your prompt response and confirming a seat for your child(ren) in the next academic
                 year with us. We wish your child(ren) better prospects in the next grade and together we will ensure
                 the best of learning for them.</p>
                <p></p>
                
            </div>
            ]]></field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>

